<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>

<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<channel>
   
      <title>https://fantasy11team.com/</title>
   
   <link>https://fantasy11team.com/</link>
   <description>Platform to help build a better dream team</description>
   <language>en-uk</language>
   
   <title>
   <![CDATA[ Fantasy11Team.com ]]>
   </title>
   <description>
   <![CDATA[ Platform to help build a better dream team ]]>
   </description>
   <link>https://fantasy11team.com/</link>
   <image>
   <url>https://fantasy11team.com/assets/images/favicon.png</url>
   <title>Fantasy11Team.com</title>
   <link>https://fantasy11team.com/</link>
   </image>
   <generator>Jekyll 3.6.2</generator>
   <lastBuildDate></lastBuildDate>
   <atom:link href="https://fantasy11team.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
   <ttl>60</ttl>
   <atom:link href="rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
   
	<item>
	  <title>IN vs SA First ODI, Today's Match, Dream Team, Prediction</title>
	  <link>https://fantasy11team.com/India-vs-South-Africa-First-ODI</link>
		
				
		
				
						<author>Rexer</author>
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
	  <pubDate>2018-02-01T02:00:00+05:30</pubDate>
	  <guid>https://fantasy11team.com/India-vs-South-Africa-First-ODI</guid>
	  <description><![CDATA[
	     <p>Hello and Welcome to the first ODI match preview of 6 ODI match series between India and South Africa.</p>

<p>India has played 7 ODIs on this ground with 6 loss and 1 no result. While South Africa scored above 300 in 50-over format with centuries from Faf du Plesis and David Miller. India has already lost the test series to South Africa by 2-1. But India’s win in the last test match have given a lot of confidence to the guests.</p>

<p>While hosts will be looking to continue their dominance as ODI top team, India will also be using this series to be the number 1 ODI team in the World.</p>

<p>We will be providing match predictions, probable XI, tips and some tricks to help you win big in this match.</p>

<h6 id="important"><u>Important</u></h6>
<p><em>AB de Villiers</em> will not be playing first three ODI matches agains India due to injury. Khaya Zondo is expected to make his debut.</p>

<h6 id="event-details"><u>Event Details</u></h6>

<blockquote>
  <p><strong>Indis vs South Africa ODI Series</strong> <em>IN vs SA</em></p>
  <ul>
    <li>Kingsmead, Durban</li>
    <li>Date: Feb 1, 04:30 PM IST</li>
  </ul>
</blockquote>

<h6 id="venue-odi-stats"><u>Venue ODI Stats</u></h6>
<blockquote>
  <ul>
    <li>Total matches	43</li>
    <li>Matches won batting first	21</li>
    <li>Matches won bowling first	16</li>
    <li>Average 1st Inns scores	237</li>
    <li>Average 2nd Inns scores	183</li>
  </ul>
</blockquote>

<h6 id="squads"><u>Squads</u></h6>
<blockquote>
  <p><strong>India</strong>:
Virat Kohli (capt), Rohit Sharma, Jasprit Bumrah, Yuzvendra Chahal, Shikhar Dhawan, MS Dhoni (wk), Shreyas Iyer, Kedar Jadhav, Dinesh Karthik, Kuldeep Yadav, Bhuvneshwar Kumar, Mohammed Shami, Manish Pandey, Hardik Pandya, Axar Patel, Ajinkya Rahane, Shardul Thakur.</p>
</blockquote>

<blockquote>
  <p><strong>South Africa</strong>:
Faf du Plessis (capt), Hashim Amla, Quinton de Kock (wk), JP Duminy, Imran Tahir, Aiden Markram, David Miller, Morne Morkel, Chris Morris, Lungi Ngidi, Andile Phehlukwayo, Kagiso Rabada, Tabraiz Shamsi, Khaya Zondo.</p>
</blockquote>

<h6 id="key-players"><u>Key Players</u></h6>
<blockquote>
  <p><strong>India</strong>: Virat Kohli, Rohit Sharma, M Shami
<strong>South Africa</strong>: Q De Kock, Faf du Plessis, Rabada</p>
</blockquote>

<h6 id="st-w-vs-ps-w-probable-playing-xi-"><u>ST-W vs PS-W Probable Playing XI :</u></h6>
<blockquote>
  <p><strong>India:</strong>
Virat Kohli (capt), Rohit Sharma, Jasprit Bumrah, Yuzvendra Chahal, Shikhar Dhawan, MS Dhoni (wk), Kedar Jadhav, Bhuvneshwar Kumar, Mohammed Shami, Manish Pandey, Hardik Pandya.</p>
</blockquote>

<blockquote>
  <p><strong>South Africa:</strong>
Faf du Plessis (capt), Hashim Amla, Quinton de Kock (wk), JP Duminy, Imran Tahir, David Miller, Morne Morkel, Chris Morris, Lungi Ngidi, Andile Phehlukwayo, Kagiso Rabada.</p>
</blockquote>

<h6 id="dream-team"><u>Dream Team</u></h6>

<p><img src="assets/images/ind-vs-sa-010218.png" alt="IN vs SA 1st ODI" /></p>

<h6 id="suggestions"><u>Suggestions</u></h6>
<blockquote>
  <ul>
    <li>R Priest is the only option as wicket keeper.</li>
    <li>In Batsmens N Bolton, E Villani, R Haynes, A Blackwell and N Stalenberg are good.</li>
    <li>K Brunt, N Sciver, N Carey, S Taylor and H Graham are good all-rounders.</li>
    <li>In bowlers R Farrell, S Bates, P Cleary, E King, B Vakarewa and T Newton are good choice.</li>
    <li>If you want you can change Captain and Vc as you like.</li>
  </ul>
</blockquote>

<p>Let us know your favourite team and your favourite players.</p>

	  ]]></description>
	</item>

	<item>
	  <title>PS-W vs ST-W Aus Women T20 Bash WBBL 2017-18 1st Semi Final, Today's Match, Dream Team, Prediction</title>
	  <link>https://fantasy11team.com/ST-W-vs-PS-W-Semi-Final</link>
		
				
		
				
						<author>Rexer</author>
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
	  <pubDate>2018-01-31T15:30:00+05:30</pubDate>
	  <guid>https://fantasy11team.com/ST-W-vs-PS-W-Semi-Final</guid>
	  <description><![CDATA[
	     <p>Welcome to the 1st Semi Final of Australia Women Big Bash 2017-18 between Sydney Thunders and Perth Scorchers.
This is third season of WBBL where ST is going to lock horn with PS in the semi final match</p>

<p>We will be providing match predictions, probable XI, tips and some tricks to help you win big in this match.</p>

<h6 id="important"><u>Important</u></h6>
<p>The road to finals (most recent last):</p>
<ul>
  <li><strong>Sydney Thunder</strong>:WLWWWWWLWWLWLW</li>
  <li><strong>Perth Scorchers</strong>: WWLWLWLWLLWWLW</li>
  <li><strong>Overall head to head</strong>: Thunder 5, Scorchers 2</li>
</ul>

<h6 id="point-table"><u>Point Table</u></h6>

<table>
  <thead>
    <tr>
      <th>Teams</th>
      <th>Mat</th>
      <th>Won</th>
      <th>Lost</th>
      <th>Tied</th>
    </tr>
  </thead>
  <tbody>
    <tr>
      <td>Sydney Sixers Women</td>
      <td>14</td>
      <td>10</td>
      <td>4</td>
      <td>0</td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>Sydney Thunder Women</td>
      <td>14</td>
      <td>10</td>
      <td>4</td>
      <td>0</td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>Perth Scorchers Women</td>
      <td>14</td>
      <td>8</td>
      <td>6</td>
      <td>0</td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>Adelaide Strikers Women</td>
      <td>14</td>
      <td>8</td>
      <td>6</td>
      <td>0</td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>Brisbane Heat Women</td>
      <td>14</td>
      <td>7</td>
      <td>7</td>
      <td>0</td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>Melbourne Renegades Women</td>
      <td>14</td>
      <td>6</td>
      <td>8</td>
      <td>0</td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>Melbourne Stars Women</td>
      <td>14</td>
      <td>5</td>
      <td>9</td>
      <td>0</td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>Hobart Hurricanes Women</td>
      <td>14</td>
      <td>2</td>
      <td>12</td>
      <td>0</td>
    </tr>
  </tbody>
</table>

<h6 id="event-details"><u>Event Details</u></h6>

<blockquote>
  <p><strong>Australia Women Big Bash 2017-18</strong> <em>PS-W vs ST-W</em></p>
  <ul>
    <li>Perth Stadium(Optus Stadium), Perth</li>
    <li>Date: Feb 1, 09:40 AM IST</li>
  </ul>
</blockquote>

<h6 id="squads"><u>Squads</u></h6>
<blockquote>
  <p><strong>Sydney Thunders</strong>:
Alex Blackwell (C), Sam Bates, Nicola Carey, Rene Farrell, Maisy Gibson, Lisa Griffith, Rachael Haynes, Rachel Priest, Naomi Stalenberg, Stafanie Taylor, Rachel Trenaman, Belinda Vakarewa, Fran Wilson</p>
</blockquote>

<blockquote>
  <p><strong>Perth Scorchers</strong>:
Elyse Villani (C), Megan Banting, Nicole Bolton, Katherine Brunt, Piepa Cleary, Lauren Ebsary, Heather Graham, Emma King, Thamsyn Newton, Taneale Peschel, Chloe Piparo, Natalie Sciver, Emily Smith</p>
</blockquote>

<h6 id="key-players"><u>Key Players</u></h6>
<blockquote>
  <p><strong>Sydney Thunders</strong>: Rachael Haynes, Rene Farrell, Rachel Priest, Alex Blackwell, S Taylor, N Carey, Rene Farrell</p>
</blockquote>

<blockquote>
  <p><strong>Perth Scorchers</strong>: Katherine Brunt, Nicole Bolton, Elyse Villani, K Brunt, N Sciver, H Graham</p>
</blockquote>

<h6 id="st-w-vs-ps-w-probable-playing-xi-"><u>ST-W vs PS-W Probable Playing XI :</u></h6>
<blockquote>
  <p><strong>Sydney Thunders:</strong>
Stafanie Taylor, Rachael Haynes, Alex Blackwell (c), Rachel Priest (wk), Rene Farrell, Fran Wilson, Nicola Carey, Belinda Vakarewa, Maisy Gibson, Samantha Bates, Lisa Griffith</p>
</blockquote>

<blockquote>
  <p><strong>Perth Scorchers:</strong>
Elyse Villani (c), Katherine Brunt, Natalie Sciver, Nicole Bolton, Thamsyn Newton, Megan Banting, Piepa Cleary, Lauren Ebsary, Heather Graham, Emma King, Emily Smith (wk)</p>
</blockquote>

<h6 id="dream-team"><u>Dream Team</u></h6>

<p><img src="assets/images/st-w-vs-ps-w-310118.png" alt="ST-W vs PS-W WBBL Semi" /></p>

<h6 id="suggestions"><u>Suggestions</u></h6>
<blockquote>
  <ul>
    <li>R Priest is the only option as wicket keeper.</li>
    <li>In Batsmens N Bolton, E Villani, R Haynes, A Blackwell and N Stalenberg are good.</li>
    <li>K Brunt, N Sciver, N Carey, S Taylor and H Graham are good all-rounders.</li>
    <li>In bowlers R Farrell, S Bates, P Cleary, E King, B Vakarewa and T Newton are good choice.</li>
    <li>If you want you can change Captain and Vc as you like.</li>
  </ul>
</blockquote>

<p>Let us know your favourite team and your favourite players.</p>

	  ]]></description>
	</item>

	<item>
	  <title>AF-Y vs PK-Y Under 19 ICC 3rd Place Playoff, Today's Match, Dream Team, Prediction</title>
	  <link>https://fantasy11team.com/AFGU19-vs-APKU19</link>
		
				
		
				
						<author>Rexer</author>
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
	  <pubDate>2018-01-31T13:00:00+05:30</pubDate>
	  <guid>https://fantasy11team.com/AFGU19-vs-APKU19</guid>
	  <description><![CDATA[
	     <p>Welcome to the 3rd place playoff of 2018 Under 19 ICC Cricket World Cup between Afghanistan and Pakistan.
Both the teams have lost their respective semi-finals of the tournament and now looking for the 3rd place.</p>

<p>Afghanistan will be facing the Pakistan for the 2nd time in the tournament and will be aiming for the second victort over Pakistan. Afghanistan has been a secret superstar in this season as they have lost only match. Pakistan started the season with a loss but picked up very quickly and reached the semi-final.</p>

<p>We will be providing match predictions, probable XI, tips and some tricks to help you win big in this match.
Heavy rain showers are expected through the course of the day.</p>

<h5 id="event-details">Event Details</h5>
<p><strong>ICC Under 19 World Cup</strong> <em>AF-Y vs PK-y</em></p>
<ul>
  <li>Queenstown Events Centre, Queenstown</li>
  <li>Date: Jan30, 3:00 AM IST</li>
</ul>

<h5 id="venue-odi-stats">Venue ODI Stats</h5>
<ul>
  <li>Total matches	9</li>
  <li>Matches won batting first	1</li>
  <li>Matches won bowling first	6</li>
  <li>Average 1st Inns scores	164</li>
  <li>Average 2nd Inns scores	168</li>
</ul>

<h5 id="squads">Squads</h5>
<h6 id="afghanistan-u19">Afghanistan U19:</h6>
<p>Naveen-ul-Haq (c), Qais Ahmad, Azmatullah Omarzai, Ikram Ali Khil (wk), Rahmanullah, Mohammad Ibrahim, Zahir Khan, Darwish Rasooli, Baheer Shah, Tariq Stanikzai, Nisar Wahdat, Wafadar, Waqarullah Ishaq, Mujeeb Zadran, Yousuf Zazai</p>

<h6 id="pakistan-u19">Pakistan U19:</h6>
<p>Muhammad Zaid Alam, Imran Shah, Rohail Nazir (wk), Ali Zaryab, Mohammad Taha, Ammad Alam, Saad Khan, Hasan Khan (c), Muhammad Musa, Shaheen Afridi, Arshad Iqbal, Suleman Shafqat, Mohammad Ali Khan, Munir Riaz, Muhammad Mohsin Khan</p>

<h5 id="key-players">Key Players</h5>
<h6 id="afghanistan-u19-1">Afghanistan U19:</h6>
<ul>
  <li>Ikram Ali Khil</li>
  <li>Rahmanullah</li>
  <li>Mujeeb Zadran</li>
  <li>Qasi Ahmed</li>
  <li>Ibrahim Zadran</li>
</ul>

<h6 id="pakistan-u19-1">Pakistan U19:</h6>
<ul>
  <li>Muhammad Musa</li>
  <li>Arshad Iqbal</li>
  <li>Hasan Khan</li>
  <li>Shaheen Afridi</li>
  <li>Ali Zaryab</li>
</ul>

<h5 id="afg-y-vs-pak-y-probable-playing-xi-">Afg-Y vs Pak-Y Probable Playing XI :</h5>
<h6 id="afghanistan-u19-2">Afghanistan U19:</h6>
<p>Zahir Khan, Ikram Ali Khil (wk), Naveen-ul-Haq (c), Darwish Rasooli, Mujeeb Zadran, Nisar Wahdat, Qais Ahmad, Ibrahim Zadran, Rahmanullah, Azmatullah, Baheer Shah</p>

<h6 id="pakistan-u19-2">Pakistan U19:</h6>
<p>Hasan Khan (c), Muhammad Musa, Muhammad Zaid Alam, Saad Khan, Shaheen Afridi, Rohail Nazir (wk), Mohammad Taha, Ali Zaryab , Ammad Alam, Arshad Iqbal, Imran Shah</p>

<h5 id="dream-teams">Dream Teams</h5>

<p><img src="assets/images/afg-vs-pak-310118.png" alt="Dream Tems" /></p>

<h5 id="suggestions">Suggestions</h5>
<ul>
  <li>Both the wicket keepers are good. You can choose either one.</li>
  <li>Ibrahim Zadran, Ali Zaryab, Darwish Rasooli and Rahmanullah are good choice in batting.</li>
  <li>Azmatullah and Hasan Khan are all rounder selections.</li>
  <li>Shaheen, Musa, Qasi and Mujeeb are the bset bowlers.</li>
</ul>

<p>Let us know your favourite team and your favourite players.</p>

	  ]]></description>
	</item>

	<item>
	  <title>AUK vs NK 15th Match New Zealand ODD The Ford Cup Dream 11 Fantasy 11 Dream Team Preview</title>
	  <link>https://fantasy11team.com/aa-nd</link>
		
				
		
				
						<author>Rexer</author>
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
	  <pubDate>2018-01-30T09:30:00+05:30</pubDate>
	  <guid>https://fantasy11team.com/aa-nd</guid>
	  <description><![CDATA[
	     <hr />

<p>Welcome to the 15th Match of The Ford Cup New Zealand ODD. The match will be played between Northern Knights and Auckland. Both the teams have lost their last match so there might be some changes in the playing XI.</p>

<p>Auckland has won 2 of thier matches out of 4 and is on no. 2 in the point tables while Northern Knights has won 3 matches till now and is in the second spot. We will be providing you details about the probable 11, Dream 11 team, best fantasy team and the strong players from each squad.</p>

<h5 id="event-details">Event Details</h5>
<p><strong>Ford Cup New Zealand ODD</strong> <em>AUK vs NK</em></p>
<ul>
  <li>Cobham Oval, Whangarei</li>
  <li>Date: Jan 31, 3:30 AM IST</li>
</ul>

<h5 id="squads">Squads</h5>
<h6 id="northern-knights">Northern Knights:</h6>
<p>BJ Watling, Tim Seifert(w), Nicholas Frederick Kelly, Anton Devcich, Dean Brownlie(c), Daryl Mitchell, Scott Kuggeleijn, Brett Hampton, Joe Walker, Brent Arnel, Brett Randell, James Baker, Zak Gibson</p>

<h6 id="auckland">Auckland:</h6>
<p>Jeet Raval, Graeme Beghin, Glenn Phillips(w), Sean Solia, Mark Chapman, Craig Cachopa(c), Michael Barry, Donovan Grobbelaar, Tarun Nethula, Ben Lister, Jamie Brown, Danru Ferns, Michael Guptill-Bunce, Ben Horne, Mitchell McClenaghan, Lockie Ferguson, Matt McEwan, Robert ODonnell, Aniket Parikh</p>

<h5 id="key-players">Key Players</h5>
<h6 id="northern-knights-1">Northern Knights:</h6>
<ul>
  <li>BJ Watling</li>
  <li>Daryl Mitchell</li>
  <li>Anton Devcich</li>
  <li>Brent Arnel</li>
</ul>

<h6 id="auckland-1">Auckland:</h6>
<ul>
  <li>Glenn Phillips</li>
  <li>Mark Chapman</li>
  <li>Tarun Nethula</li>
</ul>

<h5 id="auk-vs-nk-probable-playing-xi-">AUK vs NK Probable Playing XI :</h5>
<h6 id="northern-knights-2">Northern Knights:</h6>
<p>BJ Watling, Tim Seifert(w), Nicholas Frederick Kelly, Anton Devcich, Dean Brownlie(c), Daryl Mitchell, Scott Kuggeleijn, Brett Hampton, Joe Walker, Brent Arnel, Brett Randell</p>

<h6 id="auckland-2">Auckland:</h6>
<p>Jeet Raval, Graeme Beghin, Glenn Phillips(w), Sean Solia, Mark Chapman, Craig Cachopa(c), Michael Barry, Donovan Grobbelaar, Tarun Nethula, Ben Lister, Jamie Brown</p>

<h5 id="dream-teams">Dream Teams</h5>

<p><img src="assets/images/auk-vs-nk-15.png" alt="Dream Tems" /></p>

<h5 id="suggestions">Suggestions</h5>
<ul>
  <li>For Wicket Keeper, Tim Seifert is the only choice.</li>
  <li>On batting front, BJ Watling, Glenn Phillips are good chioice.</li>
  <li>Anton Devcich, Daryl Mitchell and Mark Chapman good for all rounder.</li>
  <li>Brett Randell and Sean Solia as bowlers.</li>
</ul>

<p>Let us know your favourite team and your favourite players. You can contact us for any suggestion or query.</p>

	  ]]></description>
	</item>

	<item>
	  <title>OTG vs WEL 14th Match New Zealand ODD The Ford Cup Dream 11 Fantasy 11 Dream Team Preview</title>
	  <link>https://fantasy11team.com/wel-vs-otg</link>
		
				
		
				
						<author>Rexer</author>
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
	  <pubDate>2018-01-30T08:30:00+05:30</pubDate>
	  <guid>https://fantasy11team.com/wel-vs-otg</guid>
	  <description><![CDATA[
	     <hr />

<p>Welcome to the 14th Match of The Ford Cup New Zealand ODD. The match will be played between Wellington and Otago. Both the teams have lost their last match so there might be some changes in the playing XI.</p>

<p>Otago has won 2 of thier matches out of 4 and is on no. 3 in the point tables while Wellington has won only 1 match till now and is in the second last spot. We will be providing you details about the probable 11, Dream 11 team, best fantasy team and the strong players from each squad.</p>

<h5 id="event-details">Event Details</h5>
<p><strong>Ford Cup New Zealand ODD</strong> <em>OTG vs WEL</em></p>
<ul>
  <li>Basin Reserve, Wellington</li>
  <li>Date: Jan 31, 3:30 AM IST</li>
</ul>

<h5 id="venue-odi-stats">Venue ODI Stats</h5>
<ul>
  <li>Total matches	29</li>
  <li>Matches won batting first	15</li>
  <li>Matches won bowling first	11</li>
  <li>Average 1st Inns scores	217</li>
  <li>Average 2nd Inns scores	178</li>
</ul>

<h5 id="squads">Squads</h5>
<h6 id="otago">Otago:</h6>
<p>Rob Nicol(c), Hamish Rutherford, Shawn Hicks, Neil Broom, Derek de Boorder(w), James Neesham, Michael Rippon, Neil Wagner, Jack Hunter, Matthew Bacon, Warren Barnes, Anaru Kitchen, Brad Wilson, Mark Craig, Michael Rae</p>

<h6 id="wellington">Wellington:</h6>
<p>Hamish Marshall(c), Malcolm Nofal, Stephen Murdoch, Devon Conway(w), Michael Bracewell,Luke Woodcock, Logan van Beek, Peter Younghusband, Ollie Newton, Ian McPeake, Hamish Bennett, Anurag Verma, Peter Young-Husband</p>

<h5 id="key-players">Key Players</h5>
<h6 id="otago-1">Otago:</h6>
<ul>
  <li>Rob Nicol</li>
  <li>Hamish Rutherford</li>
  <li>Shawn Hicks</li>
</ul>

<h6 id="wellington-1">Wellington:</h6>
<ul>
  <li>Hamish Marshall</li>
  <li>Michael Bracewell</li>
  <li>D Conway</li>
  <li>Logan Van Beek</li>
</ul>

<h5 id="otg-vs-wel-probable-playing-xi-">OTG vs Wel Probable Playing XI :</h5>
<h6 id="otago-2">Otago:</h6>
<p>Rob Nicol(c), Hamish Rutherford, Shawn Hicks, Neil Broom, Derek de Boorder(w), James Neesham, Michael Rippon, Matthew Bacon, Michael Rae, Neil Wagner, Jack Hunter</p>

<h6 id="wellington-2">Wellington:</h6>
<p>Hamish Marshall(c), Malcolm Nofal, Stephen Murdoch, Devon Conway(w), Michael Bracewell, Fraser Colson/Alex Ridley, Luke Woodcock, Logan van Beek, Ian McPeake, Peter Younghusband, Ollie Newton</p>

<h5 id="dream-teams">Dream Teams</h5>

<p><img src="assets/images/otg-vs-wel-14.png" alt="Dream Tems" /></p>

<h5 id="suggestions">Suggestions</h5>
<ul>
  <li>For Wicket Keeper, D Conway would be better choice.</li>
  <li>On batting front, Neil, Marshal and Rutherford are good.</li>
  <li>Rob Nicol is best in all rounder.</li>
  <li>Lon Beek is the bowling option.</li>
</ul>

<p>Let us know your favourite team and your favourite players. You can contact us for any suggestion or query.</p>

	  ]]></description>
	</item>

	<item>
	  <title>CD vs CTB 13th Match New Zealand ODD The Ford Cup Dream 11 Fantasy 11 Dream Team Preview</title>
	  <link>https://fantasy11team.com/cd-ca</link>
		
				
		
				
						<author>Rexer</author>
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
	  <pubDate>2018-01-30T07:30:00+05:30</pubDate>
	  <guid>https://fantasy11team.com/cd-ca</guid>
	  <description><![CDATA[
	     <hr />

<p>Welcome to the 13th Match of The Ford Cup New Zealand ODD. The match will be played between Central District and Canterbury. Both the teams have won their last match so there might not be any change in the playing XI.</p>

<p>Central District is on the top in the point tables while Canterbury is in the last spot. We will be providing you details about the probable 11, Dream 11 team, best fantasy team and the strong players from each squad.</p>

<h5 id="event-details">Event Details</h5>
<p><strong>Ford Cup New Zealand ODD</strong> <em>CD vs CTB</em></p>
<ul>
  <li>Fitzherbert Park, Palmerston North</li>
  <li>Date: Jan 31, 3:30 AM IST</li>
</ul>

<h5 id="squads">Squads</h5>
<h6 id="canterbury">Canterbury:</h6>
<p>Michael Pollard, Chad Bowes, Andrew Ellis(c), Henry Nicholls, Tom Latham(w), Todd Astle, Cam Fletcher, Cole McConchie, Tim Johnston, Matt Henry, Ed Nuttall, Kyle Jamieson, Jeremy Benton, Leo Carter, Michael Davidson, Fraser Sheat, Will Williams</p>

<h6 id="central-districts">Central Districts:</h6>
<p>George Worker, Ben Smith, Jesse Ryder, Will Young(c), Dane Cleaver(w), Josh Clarkson, Adam Milne, Bevan Small, Seth Rance, Ajaz Patel, Blair Tickner, Doug Bracewell, Navin Patel, Ryan McCone</p>

<h5 id="team-news">Team News</h5>
<p>Seth Rance, Bevan Small and Will Williams will not be playing. They have been replaced in the squad.</p>

<h5 id="key-players">Key Players</h5>
<h6 id="canterbury-1">Canterbury:</h6>
<ul>
  <li>Chad Bowes</li>
  <li>Michael Pollard</li>
  <li>Todd Astle</li>
  <li>Ed Nuttall</li>
</ul>

<h6 id="central-districts-1">Central Districts:</h6>
<ul>
  <li>Will Young</li>
  <li>Josh Clarkson</li>
  <li>Dean Cleaver</li>
</ul>

<h5 id="cd-vs-ctb-probable-playing-xi-">CD vs CTB Probable Playing XI :</h5>
<h6 id="canterbury-2">Canterbury:</h6>
<p>Michael Pollard, Chad Bowes, Andrew Ellis(c), Henry Nicholls, Tom Latham(w), Todd Astle, Cam Fletcher,Cole McConchie, Tim Johnston, Matt Henry, Ed Nuttall</p>

<h6 id="central-districts-2">Central Districts:</h6>
<p>George Worker, Ben Smith, Jesse Ryder, Will Young(c), Dane Cleaver(w), Josh Clarkson, Adam Milne, Ajaz Patel, Blair Tickner,  Navin Patel, Ryan McCone</p>

<h5 id="dream-teams">Dream Teams</h5>

<p><img src="assets/images/cd-vs-can-11.png" alt="Dream Tems" /></p>

<h5 id="suggestions">Suggestions</h5>
<ul>
  <li>For Wicket Keeper, Dane Cleaver is the only choice.</li>
  <li>On batting front, C Bowes, M Pollard and J Clarkson are good chioice.</li>
  <li>G Worker and T Astle are options of all-rounder.</li>
  <li>A Patel and M Henry good options as bowlers.</li>
</ul>

<p>Let us know your favourite team and your favourite players. You can contact us for any suggestion or query.</p>

	  ]]></description>
	</item>

	<item>
	  <title>SA-Y vs BAN-Y Under19 5th Place Playoff Dream 11 Fantasy 11 Dream Team Preview</title>
	  <link>https://fantasy11team.com/sa-vs-ban_u19</link>
		
				
		
				
						<author>Rexer</author>
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
	  <pubDate>2018-01-30T06:30:00+05:30</pubDate>
	  <guid>https://fantasy11team.com/sa-vs-ban_u19</guid>
	  <description><![CDATA[
	     <hr />

<p>Welcome to the 5th place playoff of ICC Under19 Cricket World Cup. The match will be played between South Africa and Bangladesh.
Both the team are already out of the tournament and are fighting for the 5th place in the table. Both the teams have won their last match so there might not be any change in the playing XI.</p>

<p>Bangladesh was on second number in the group D and South Africa also placed itself at no. 2 in the Group A. Both the team posses  good bowling attack however South Africa is strong on batting front end as well. We will be providing you details about the probable 11, Dream 11 team, best fantasy team and the strong players from each squad.</p>

<h5 id="event-details">Event Details</h5>
<p><strong>Under19 ICC Cricket World Cup 2018</strong> <em>South Africa vs Bangladesh</em></p>
<ul>
  <li>Queenstown Events Centre, Queenstown</li>
  <li>Date: Jan 31, 3:00 AM IST</li>
</ul>

<h5 id="venue-odi-stats">Venue ODI Stats</h5>
<ul>
  <li>Total matches	9</li>
  <li>Matches won batting first	1</li>
  <li>Matches won bowling first	6</li>
  <li>Average 1st Inns scores	164</li>
  <li>Average 2nd Inns scores	168</li>
</ul>

<h5 id="squads">Squads</h5>
<h6 id="south-africa">South Africa:</h6>
<p>Jiveshan Pillay, Matthew Breetzke, Raynard van Tonder(c), Wandile Makwetu(w), Gerald Coetzee, Jean du Plessis, Jason Niemand, Kenan Smith, Andile Mokgakane, Jade de Klerk, Akhona Mnyaka, Fraser Jones, Thando Ntini, Hermann Rolfes, Kgaudise Molefe</p>

<h6 id="bangladesh">Bangladesh:</h6>
<p>Pinak Ghosh, Saif Hassan(c), Aminul Islam, Towhid Hridoy, Afif Hossain, Mohammad Rakib, Shakil Hossain(w), Qazi Onik, Robiul Haque, Hasan Mahmud, Tipu Sultan, Roni Hossen, Nayeem Hasan, Mahidul Islam Ankon, Mohammad Naim</p>

<h5 id="key-players">Key Players</h5>
<h6 id="south-africa-1">South Africa:</h6>
<ul>
  <li>Wandile Makwetu</li>
  <li>Raynard van Tonder</li>
  <li>Matthew Breetzke</li>
  <li>Gerald Coetzee</li>
</ul>

<h6 id="bangladesh-1">Bangladesh:</h6>
<ul>
  <li>Afif Hossain</li>
  <li>Towhid Hridoy</li>
  <li>Qazi Onik</li>
</ul>

<h5 id="sa-u19-vs-ban-u19-probable-playing-xi-">SA U19 vs BAN U19 Probable Playing XI :</h5>
<h6 id="south-africa-2">South Africa:</h6>
<p>Jiveshan Pillay, Matthew Breetzke, Raynard van Tonder(c), Wandile Makwetu(w), Gerald Coetzee, Jean du Plessis, Jason Niemand, Kenan Smith, Andile Mokgakane, Jade de Klerk, Akhona Mnyaka</p>

<h6 id="bangladesh-2">Bangladesh:</h6>
<p>Pinak Ghosh, Saif Hassan(c), Aminul Islam, Towhid Hridoy, Afif Hossain, Mohammad Rakib, Shakil Hossain(w), Qazi Onik, Robiul Haque, Hasan Mahmud, Tipu Sultan</p>

<h5 id="dream-teams">Dream Teams</h5>

<p><img src="assets/images/sa-vs-ban-u19.png" alt="Dream Tems" /></p>

<h5 id="suggestions">Suggestions</h5>
<ul>
  <li>For Wicket Keeper, Wandile Makwetu is the only choice.</li>
  <li>On batting front, Matthew Breetzke, Raynard van Tonder and Towhid Hridoy are good chioice.</li>
  <li>Saif Hassan can also be selected as he is a bowler also.</li>
  <li>There is obvious choice in all rounders section - Afif Hossain and Hermann Rolfes.</li>
  <li>Gerald Coetzee and Qazi Onik are good options as bowlers.</li>
</ul>

<p>Let us know your favourite team and your favourite players. You can contact us for any suggestion or query.</p>

	  ]]></description>
	</item>

	<item>
	  <title>ENG-Y vs NZ-Y Under 19 ICC 7th Place Playoff, Today's Match, Dream Team, Prediction</title>
	  <link>https://fantasy11team.com/engU19-vs-nzU19</link>
		
				
		
				
						<author>Rexer</author>
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
	  <pubDate>2018-01-29T11:30:00+05:30</pubDate>
	  <guid>https://fantasy11team.com/engU19-vs-nzU19</guid>
	  <description><![CDATA[
	     <p>Welcome to the 7th place playoff 2018 Under 19 ICC Cricket World Cup between England and New Zealand.
We will be providing match predictions, probable XI, tips and some tricks to help you win big in this match.
Both New Zealand and England have lost their last match which was for the 5th position.</p>

<h5 id="event-details">Event Details</h5>
<p><strong>ICC Under 19 World Cup</strong> <em>Eng-Y vs NZ-y</em></p>
<ul>
  <li>Queenstown Events Centre, Queenstown</li>
  <li>Date: Jan30, 3:00 AM IST</li>
</ul>

<h5 id="squads">Squads</h5>
<h6 id="england-u19">England U19:</h6>
<p>Tom Banton, Liam Banks, Harry Brook(c), Will Jacks, Euan Woods, Finlay Trenouth, Jack Davies(w), Prem Sisodiya, Adam Finch, Ethan Bamber, Dillon Pennington, Savin Perera, Tom Scriven, Roman Walker, Luke Hollman</p>

<h6 id="new-zealand-u19">New Zealand U19:</h6>
<p>Jakob Bhula, Rachin Ravindra, Finn Allen, Kaylum Boshier(c), Sandeep Patel, Dale Phillips, Luke Georgeson, Callum McLachlan(w), Felix Murray, Ben Lockrose, Matthew Fisher, Max Chu, Katene Clarke, Todd Watson, Connor Sullivan</p>

<h5 id="key-players">Key Players</h5>
<h6 id="england-u19-1">England U19:</h6>
<ul>
  <li>Liam Banks</li>
  <li>Will Jacks</li>
  <li>Harry Brooks</li>
  <li>Ethan Bamber</li>
</ul>

<h6 id="new-zealand-u19-1">New Zealand U19:</h6>
<ul>
  <li>Finn Allen</li>
  <li>Felix Murray</li>
  <li>Matthew Fisher</li>
  <li>Jacob Bhula</li>
  <li>Rachin Ravindra</li>
</ul>

<h5 id="eng-y-vs-nz-y-probable-playing-xi-">Eng-Y vs NZ-Y Probable Playing XI :</h5>
<h6 id="england-u19-2">England U19:</h6>
<p>Tom Banton, Liam Banks, Harry Brook(c), Will Jacks, Euan Woods, Finlay Trenouth, Jack Davies(w), Prem Sisodiya, Adam Finch, Ethan Bamber, Dillon Pennington,</p>

<h6 id="new-zealand-u19-2">New Zealand U19:</h6>
<p>Jakob Bhula, Rachin Ravindra, Finn Allen, Kaylum Boshier(c), Sandeep Patel, Dale Phillips, Luke Georgeson, Callum McLachlan(w), Felix Murray, Ben Lockrose, Matthew Fishe</p>

<h5 id="dream-teams">Dream Teams</h5>

<p><img src="assets/images/eng-vs-nz.png" alt="Dream Tems" /></p>

<h5 id="suggestions">Suggestions</h5>
<ul>
  <li>Both the wicket keepers are at same level and any one can be selected.</li>
  <li>Finn Allen, L Banks and D Philips are good choice for batsmen.</li>
  <li>In All rounders, Ravindra, Bhula, H Brooks and W Jacks are good.</li>
  <li>Bamber and Fisher are the best choices</li>
</ul>

<p>Let us know your favourite team and your favourite players.</p>

	  ]]></description>
	</item>

	<item>
	  <title>IND-Y vs PAK-Y Under 19 ICC Semi-Final, Today's Match, Dream Team, Prediction</title>
	  <link>https://fantasy11team.com/IndU19-vs-paku19</link>
		
				
		
				
						<author>Rexer</author>
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
	  <pubDate>2018-01-29T10:30:00+05:30</pubDate>
	  <guid>https://fantasy11team.com/IndU19-vs-paku19</guid>
	  <description><![CDATA[
	     <p>Welcome to the 2nd semi-final of 2018 Under 19 ICC Cricket World Cup. 
We will be providing match predictions, probable XI, tips and some tricks to help you win big in this match.
This match is going to be awesome as it is not just an ICC event but it is India vs Pakistan.</p>

<h5 id="event-details">Event Details</h5>
<p><strong>ICC Under 19 World Cup</strong> <em>Ind-Y vs Pak-y</em></p>
<ul>
  <li>Hagley Oval, Christchurch</li>
  <li>Date: Jan30, 3:00 AM IST</li>
</ul>

<h5 id="squads">Squads</h5>
<h6 id="india-u19">India U19:</h6>
<p>Prithvi Shaw(c), Manjot Kalra, Shubman Gill, Harvik Desai(w), Riyan Parag, Abhishek Sharma, Kamlesh Nagarkoti, Anukul Sudhakar Roy, Shivam Mavi, Shiva Singh, Ishan Porel, Aryan Juyal, Arshdeep Singh, Pankaj Yadav, Himanshu Rana, Aditya Thakare</p>

<h6 id="pakistan-u19">Pakistan U19:</h6>
<p>Muhammad Zaid Alam, Rohail Nazir(w), Ammad Alam, Hasan Khan(c), Mohammad Taha, Saad Khan, Muhammad Musa, Shaheen Afridi, Suleman Shafqat, Arshad Iqbal, Imran Shah, Mohammad Ali Khan, Munir Riaz, Ali Zaryab, Muhammad Mohsin Khan</p>

<h5 id="key-players">Key Players</h5>
<h6 id="india-u19-1">India U19:</h6>
<ul>
  <li>Shubhman Gill</li>
  <li>Prthvi Shaw</li>
  <li>Anukul Sudhakar Roy</li>
  <li>Kamlesh Nagarkoti</li>
  <li>Abhishek Sharma</li>
  <li>Shivam Mavi</li>
</ul>

<h6 id="pakistan-u19-1">Pakistan U19:</h6>
<ul>
  <li>Muhammad Ziad Alam</li>
  <li>Hasan Khan</li>
  <li>Shaheen Afridi</li>
  <li>Ali Zaryab</li>
</ul>

<h5 id="ind-y-vs-pak-y-probable-playing-xi-">Ind-Y vs Pak-Y Probable Playing XI :</h5>
<h6 id="india-u19-2">India U19:</h6>
<p>Prithwi Shaw, Manjot Kalra, Shubhman Gill, H Desai, Himanshu Rana, Abhishek Sharma, Anukul Sudhakar Roy, K Nagarkoti, Shiva Singh, Shivam Mavi, Ishan Porel</p>

<h6 id="pakistan-u19-2">Pakistan U19:</h6>
<p>Muhammad Zaid Alam, Rohail Nazir, Ammad Alam/M Mohsin Khan, Ali Zaryab, Mohammad Taha, Saad Khan, Hasan Khan, Shaheen Afridi, Muhammad Musa, Suleman Shafqat/M Riyaz, Arshad Iqbal</p>

<h5 id="dream-teams">Dream Teams</h5>

<p><img src="assets/images/ind-vs-pak.png" alt="Dream Tems" /></p>

<h5 id="suggestions">Suggestions</h5>
<ul>
  <li>Both the wicket keepers H Desia and R Nazir are good.</li>
  <li>Indian batsmen would be good choice to have as they are very pro.</li>
  <li>in All rounders, Anukul, Hasan Khan and K Nagarkoti are good.</li>
  <li>S Mavi is speed star in this tournamnet so it would be good choice.</li>
</ul>

<p>Let us know your favourite team and your favourite players.</p>

	  ]]></description>
	</item>


</channel>
</rss>
