<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>

<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<channel>
   
      <title>https://fantasy11team.com/</title>
   
   <link>https://fantasy11team.com/</link>
   <description>Platform to help build a better dream team</description>
   <language>en-uk</language>
   
   <title>
   <![CDATA[ Fantasy11Team.com ]]>
   </title>
   <description>
   <![CDATA[ Platform to help build a better dream team ]]>
   </description>
   <link>https://fantasy11team.com/</link>
   <image>
   <url>https://fantasy11team.com/assets/images/favicon.png</url>
   <title>Fantasy11Team.com</title>
   <link>https://fantasy11team.com/</link>
   </image>
   <generator>Jekyll 3.6.2</generator>
   <lastBuildDate></lastBuildDate>
   <atom:link href="https://fantasy11team.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
   <ttl>60</ttl>
   <atom:link href="rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
   
	<item>
	  <title>SA-Y vs BAN-Y Under19 5th Place Playoff Dream 11 Fantasy 11 Dream Team Preview</title>
	  <link>https://fantasy11team.com/sa-vs-ban_u19</link>
		
				
		
				
						<author>Rexer</author>
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
	  <pubDate>2018-01-30T06:30:00+05:30</pubDate>
	  <guid>https://fantasy11team.com/sa-vs-ban_u19</guid>
	  <description><![CDATA[
	     <hr />

<p>Welcome to the 5th place playoff of ICC Under19 Cricket World Cup. The match will be played between South Africa and Bangladesh.
Both the team are already out of the tournament and are fighting for the 5th place in the table. Both the teams have won their last match so there might not be any change in the playing XI.</p>

<p>Bangladesh was on second number in the group D and South Africa also placed itself at no. 2 in the Group A. Both the team posses  good bowling attack however South Africa is strong on batting front end as well. We will be providing you details about the probable 11, Dream 11 team, best fantasy team and the strong players from each squad.</p>

<h5 id="event-details">Event Details</h5>
<p><strong>Under19 ICC Cricket World Cup 2018</strong> <em>South Africa vs Bangladesh</em></p>
<ul>
  <li>Queenstown Events Centre, Queenstown</li>
  <li>Date: Jan 31, 3:00 AM IST</li>
</ul>

<h5 id="venue-odi-stats">Venue ODI Stats</h5>
<ul>
  <li>Total matches	9</li>
  <li>Matches won batting first	1</li>
  <li>Matches won bowling first	6</li>
  <li>Average 1st Inns scores	164</li>
  <li>Average 2nd Inns scores	168</li>
</ul>

<h5 id="squads">Squads</h5>
<h6 id="south-africa">South Africa:</h6>
<p>Jiveshan Pillay, Matthew Breetzke, Raynard van Tonder(c), Wandile Makwetu(w), Gerald Coetzee, Jean du Plessis, Jason Niemand, Kenan Smith, Andile Mokgakane, Jade de Klerk, Akhona Mnyaka, Fraser Jones, Thando Ntini, Hermann Rolfes, Kgaudise Molefe</p>

<h6 id="bangladesh">Bangladesh:</h6>
<p>Pinak Ghosh, Saif Hassan(c), Aminul Islam, Towhid Hridoy, Afif Hossain, Mohammad Rakib, Shakil Hossain(w), Qazi Onik, Robiul Haque, Hasan Mahmud, Tipu Sultan, Roni Hossen, Nayeem Hasan, Mahidul Islam Ankon, Mohammad Naim</p>

<h5 id="key-players">Key Players</h5>
<h6 id="south-africa-1">South Africa:</h6>
<ul>
  <li>Wandile Makwetu</li>
  <li>Raynard van Tonder</li>
  <li>Matthew Breetzke</li>
  <li>Gerald Coetzee</li>
</ul>

<h6 id="bangladesh-1">Bangladesh:</h6>
<ul>
  <li>Afif Hossain</li>
  <li>Towhid Hridoy</li>
  <li>Qazi Onik</li>
</ul>

<h5 id="sa-u19-vs-ban-u19-probable-playing-xi-">SA U19 vs BAN U19 Probable Playing XI :</h5>
<h6 id="south-africa-2">South Africa:</h6>
<p>Jiveshan Pillay, Matthew Breetzke, Raynard van Tonder(c), Wandile Makwetu(w), Gerald Coetzee, Jean du Plessis, Jason Niemand, Kenan Smith, Andile Mokgakane, Jade de Klerk, Akhona Mnyaka</p>

<h6 id="bangladesh-2">Bangladesh:</h6>
<p>Pinak Ghosh, Saif Hassan(c), Aminul Islam, Towhid Hridoy, Afif Hossain, Mohammad Rakib, Shakil Hossain(w), Qazi Onik, Robiul Haque, Hasan Mahmud, Tipu Sultan</p>

<h5 id="dream-teams">Dream Teams</h5>

<p><img src="assets/images/sa-vs-ban-u19.png" alt="Dream Tems" /></p>

<h5 id="suggestions">Suggestions</h5>
<ul>
  <li>For Wicket Keeper, Wandile Makwetu is the only choice.</li>
  <li>On batting front, Matthew Breetzke, Raynard van Tonder and Towhid Hridoy are good chioice.</li>
  <li>Saif Hassan can also be selected as he is a bowler also.</li>
  <li>There is obvious choice in all rounders section - Afif Hossain and Hermann Rolfes.</li>
  <li>Gerald Coetzee and Qazi Onik are good options as bowlers.</li>
</ul>

<p>Let us know your favourite team and your favourite players. You can contact us for any suggestion or query.</p>

	  ]]></description>
	</item>

	<item>
	  <title>ENG-Y vs NZ-Y Under 19 ICC 7th Place Playoff, Today's Match, Dream Team, Prediction</title>
	  <link>https://fantasy11team.com/engU19-vs-nzU19</link>
		
				
		
				
						<author>Rexer</author>
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
	  <pubDate>2018-01-29T11:30:00+05:30</pubDate>
	  <guid>https://fantasy11team.com/engU19-vs-nzU19</guid>
	  <description><![CDATA[
	     <p>Welcome to the 7th place playoff 2018 Under 19 ICC Cricket World Cup between England and New Zealand.
We will be providing match predictions, probable XI, tips and some tricks to help you win big in this match.
Both New Zealand and England have lost their last match which was for the 5th position.</p>

<h5 id="event-details">Event Details</h5>
<p><strong>ICC Under 19 World Cup</strong> <em>Eng-Y vs NZ-y</em></p>
<ul>
  <li>Queenstown Events Centre, Queenstown</li>
  <li>Date: Jan30, 3:00 AM IST</li>
</ul>

<h5 id="squads">Squads</h5>
<h6 id="england-u19">England U19:</h6>
<p>Tom Banton, Liam Banks, Harry Brook(c), Will Jacks, Euan Woods, Finlay Trenouth, Jack Davies(w), Prem Sisodiya, Adam Finch, Ethan Bamber, Dillon Pennington, Savin Perera, Tom Scriven, Roman Walker, Luke Hollman</p>

<h6 id="new-zealand-u19">New Zealand U19:</h6>
<p>Jakob Bhula, Rachin Ravindra, Finn Allen, Kaylum Boshier(c), Sandeep Patel, Dale Phillips, Luke Georgeson, Callum McLachlan(w), Felix Murray, Ben Lockrose, Matthew Fisher, Max Chu, Katene Clarke, Todd Watson, Connor Sullivan</p>

<h5 id="key-players">Key Players</h5>
<h6 id="england-u19-1">England U19:</h6>
<ul>
  <li>Liam Banks</li>
  <li>Will Jacks</li>
  <li>Harry Brooks</li>
  <li>Ethan Bamber</li>
</ul>

<h6 id="new-zealand-u19-1">New Zealand U19:</h6>
<ul>
  <li>Finn Allen</li>
  <li>Felix Murray</li>
  <li>Matthew Fisher</li>
  <li>Jacob Bhula</li>
  <li>Rachin Ravindra</li>
</ul>

<h5 id="eng-y-vs-nz-y-probable-playing-xi-">Eng-Y vs NZ-Y Probable Playing XI :</h5>
<h6 id="england-u19-2">England U19:</h6>
<p>Tom Banton, Liam Banks, Harry Brook(c), Will Jacks, Euan Woods, Finlay Trenouth, Jack Davies(w), Prem Sisodiya, Adam Finch, Ethan Bamber, Dillon Pennington,</p>

<h6 id="new-zealand-u19-2">New Zealand U19:</h6>
<p>Jakob Bhula, Rachin Ravindra, Finn Allen, Kaylum Boshier(c), Sandeep Patel, Dale Phillips, Luke Georgeson, Callum McLachlan(w), Felix Murray, Ben Lockrose, Matthew Fishe</p>

<h5 id="dream-teams">Dream Teams</h5>

<p><img src="assets/images/eng-vs-nz.png" alt="Dream Tems" /></p>

<h5 id="suggestions">Suggestions</h5>
<ul>
  <li>Both the wicket keepers are at same level and any one can be selected.</li>
  <li>Finn Allen, L Banks and D Philips are good choice for batsmen.</li>
  <li>In All rounders, Ravindra, Bhula, H Brooks and W Jacks are good.</li>
  <li>Bamber and Fisher are the best choices</li>
</ul>

<p>Let us know your favourite team and your favourite players.</p>

	  ]]></description>
	</item>

	<item>
	  <title>IND-Y vs PAK-Y Under 19 ICC Semi-Final, Today's Match, Dream Team, Prediction</title>
	  <link>https://fantasy11team.com/IndU19-vs-paku19</link>
		
				
		
				
						<author>Rexer</author>
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
	  <pubDate>2018-01-29T10:30:00+05:30</pubDate>
	  <guid>https://fantasy11team.com/IndU19-vs-paku19</guid>
	  <description><![CDATA[
	     <p>Welcome to the 2nd semi-final of 2018 Under 19 ICC Cricket World Cup. 
We will be providing match predictions, probable XI, tips and some tricks to help you win big in this match.
This match is going to be awesome as it is not just an ICC event but it is India vs Pakistan.</p>

<h5 id="event-details">Event Details</h5>
<p><strong>ICC Under 19 World Cup</strong> <em>Ind-Y vs Pak-y</em></p>
<ul>
  <li>Hagley Oval, Christchurch</li>
  <li>Date: Jan30, 3:00 AM IST</li>
</ul>

<h5 id="squads">Squads</h5>
<h6 id="india-u19">India U19:</h6>
<p>Prithvi Shaw(c), Manjot Kalra, Shubman Gill, Harvik Desai(w), Riyan Parag, Abhishek Sharma, Kamlesh Nagarkoti, Anukul Sudhakar Roy, Shivam Mavi, Shiva Singh, Ishan Porel, Aryan Juyal, Arshdeep Singh, Pankaj Yadav, Himanshu Rana, Aditya Thakare</p>

<h6 id="pakistan-u19">Pakistan U19:</h6>
<p>Muhammad Zaid Alam, Rohail Nazir(w), Ammad Alam, Hasan Khan(c), Mohammad Taha, Saad Khan, Muhammad Musa, Shaheen Afridi, Suleman Shafqat, Arshad Iqbal, Imran Shah, Mohammad Ali Khan, Munir Riaz, Ali Zaryab, Muhammad Mohsin Khan</p>

<h5 id="key-players">Key Players</h5>
<h6 id="india-u19-1">India U19:</h6>
<ul>
  <li>Shubhman Gill</li>
  <li>Prthvi Shaw</li>
  <li>Anukul Sudhakar Roy</li>
  <li>Kamlesh Nagarkoti</li>
  <li>Abhishek Sharma</li>
  <li>Shivam Mavi</li>
</ul>

<h6 id="pakistan-u19-1">Pakistan U19:</h6>
<ul>
  <li>Muhammad Ziad Alam</li>
  <li>Hasan Khan</li>
  <li>Shaheen Afridi</li>
  <li>Ali Zaryab</li>
</ul>

<h5 id="ind-y-vs-pak-y-probable-playing-xi-">Ind-Y vs Pak-Y Probable Playing XI :</h5>
<h6 id="india-u19-2">India U19:</h6>
<p>Prithwi Shaw, Manjot Kalra, Shubhman Gill, H Desai, Himanshu Rana, Abhishek Sharma, Anukul Sudhakar Roy, K Nagarkoti, Shiva Singh, Shivam Mavi, Ishan Porel</p>

<h6 id="pakistan-u19-2">Pakistan U19:</h6>
<p>Muhammad Zaid Alam, Rohail Nazir, Ammad Alam/M Mohsin Khan, Ali Zaryab, Mohammad Taha, Saad Khan, Hasan Khan, Shaheen Afridi, Muhammad Musa, Suleman Shafqat/M Riyaz, Arshad Iqbal</p>

<h5 id="dream-teams">Dream Teams</h5>

<p><img src="assets/images/ind-vs-pak.png" alt="Dream Tems" /></p>

<h5 id="suggestions">Suggestions</h5>
<ul>
  <li>Both the wicket keepers H Desia and R Nazir are good.</li>
  <li>Indian batsmen would be good choice to have as they are very pro.</li>
  <li>in All rounders, Anukul, Hasan Khan and K Nagarkoti are good.</li>
  <li>S Mavi is speed star in this tournamnet so it would be good choice.</li>
</ul>

<p>Let us know your favourite team and your favourite players.</p>

	  ]]></description>
	</item>


</channel>
</rss>
