<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>

<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<channel>
   
      <title>https://fantasy11team.com/</title>
   
   <link>https://fantasy11team.com/</link>
   <description>Platform to help build a better dream team</description>
   <language>en-uk</language>
   
      
            
      
            
               
               
                  <managingEditor>Rexer</managingEditor>
            
      
            
      
            
      
            
      
            
      
            
      
            
      
   
   <title>
   <![CDATA[ Rexer - Fantasy11Team.com ]]>
   </title>
   <description>
   <![CDATA[ Platform to help build a better dream team ]]>
   </description>
   <link>https://fantasy11team.com/</link>
   <image>
   <url>https://fantasy11team.com/assets/images/favicon.png</url>
   <title>Rexer - Fantasy11Team.com</title>
   <link>https://fantasy11team.com/</link>
   </image>
   <generator>Jekyll 3.6.2</generator>
   <lastBuildDate></lastBuildDate>
   <atom:link href="https://fantasy11team.com/author/rexer/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
   <ttl>60</ttl>
   <atom:link href="rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
   
	<item>
	  <title>Welcome to Fantasy11team.com</title>
	  <link>https://fantasy11team.com/welcome</link>
		
				
		
				
						<author>Rexer</author>
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
	  <pubDate>2018-01-29T15:30:00+05:30</pubDate>
	  <guid>https://fantasy11team.com/welcome</guid>
	  <description><![CDATA[
	     <p>Hey! Welcome to Fantasy11test.com, it’s great to have you :)</p>

<p>We will be providing you great tips, previews and suggestions and lastest news which help you in building a great team. Good Luck!!</p>

<h3 id="there-are-a-few-things-that-we-will-be-provising-on-this-site">There are a few things that we will be provising on this site:</h3>
<ol>
  <li>News about the teams, who is in the squad, who is not playing the match, who is replacing who.</li>
  <li>Expected 11 from both the teams will be provided along with suggestions about captain and vice-captain.</li>
  <li>Our dream teams will also be published to help you out in the selection.</li>
</ol>

<p>This website has been developed using jasper2 from the github.</p>

	  ]]></description>
	</item>

	<item>
	  <title>ENG-Y vs NZ-Y Under 19 ICC 7th Place Playoff, Today's Match, Dream Team, Prediction</title>
	  <link>https://fantasy11team.com/engU19-vs-nzU19</link>
		
				
		
				
						<author>Rexer</author>
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
	  <pubDate>2018-01-29T11:30:00+05:30</pubDate>
	  <guid>https://fantasy11team.com/engU19-vs-nzU19</guid>
	  <description><![CDATA[
	     <p>Welcome to the 7th place playoff 2018 Under 19 ICC Cricket World Cup between England and New Zealand.
We will be providing match predictions, probable XI, tips and some tricks to help you win big in this match.
Both New Zealand and England have lost their last match which was for the 5th position.</p>

<h5 id="event-details">Event Details</h5>
<p><strong>ICC Under 19 World Cup</strong> <em>Eng-Y vs NZ-y</em></p>
<ul>
  <li>Queenstown Events Centre, Queenstown</li>
  <li>Date: Jan30, 3:00 AM IST</li>
</ul>

<h5 id="squads">Squads</h5>
<h6 id="england-u19">England U19:</h6>
<p>Tom Banton, Liam Banks, Harry Brook(c), Will Jacks, Euan Woods, Finlay Trenouth, Jack Davies(w), Prem Sisodiya, Adam Finch, Ethan Bamber, Dillon Pennington, Savin Perera, Tom Scriven, Roman Walker, Luke Hollman</p>

<h6 id="new-zealand-u19">New Zealand U19:</h6>
<p>Jakob Bhula, Rachin Ravindra, Finn Allen, Kaylum Boshier(c), Sandeep Patel, Dale Phillips, Luke Georgeson, Callum McLachlan(w), Felix Murray, Ben Lockrose, Matthew Fisher, Max Chu, Katene Clarke, Todd Watson, Connor Sullivan</p>

<h5 id="key-players">Key Players</h5>
<h6 id="england-u19-1">England U19:</h6>
<ul>
  <li>Liam Banks</li>
  <li>Will Jacks</li>
  <li>Harry Brooks</li>
  <li>Ethan Bamber</li>
</ul>

<h6 id="new-zealand-u19-1">New Zealand U19:</h6>
<ul>
  <li>Finn Allen</li>
  <li>Felix Murray</li>
  <li>Matthew Fisher</li>
  <li>Jacob Bhula</li>
  <li>Rachin Ravindra</li>
</ul>

<h5 id="eng-y-vs-nz-y-probable-playing-xi-">Eng-Y vs NZ-Y Probable Playing XI :</h5>
<h6 id="england-u19-2">England U19:</h6>
<p>Tom Banton, Liam Banks, Harry Brook(c), Will Jacks, Euan Woods, Finlay Trenouth, Jack Davies(w), Prem Sisodiya, Adam Finch, Ethan Bamber, Dillon Pennington,</p>

<h6 id="new-zealand-u19-2">New Zealand U19:</h6>
<p>Jakob Bhula, Rachin Ravindra, Finn Allen, Kaylum Boshier(c), Sandeep Patel, Dale Phillips, Luke Georgeson, Callum McLachlan(w), Felix Murray, Ben Lockrose, Matthew Fishe</p>

<h5 id="dream-teams">Dream Teams</h5>

<p><img src="assets/images/eng-vs-nz.png" alt="Dream Tems" /></p>

<h5 id="suggestions">Suggestions</h5>
<ul>
  <li>Both the wicket keepers are at same level and any one can be selected.</li>
  <li>Finn Allen, L Banks and D Philips are good choice for batsmen.</li>
  <li>In All rounders, Ravindra, Bhula, H Brooks and W Jacks are good.</li>
  <li>Bamber and Fisher are the best choices</li>
</ul>

<p>Let us know your favourite team and your favourite players.</p>

	  ]]></description>
	</item>

	<item>
	  <title>IND-Y vs PAK-Y Under 19 ICC Semi-Final, Today's Match, Dream Team, Prediction</title>
	  <link>https://fantasy11team.com/IndU19-vs-paku19</link>
		
				
		
				
						<author>Rexer</author>
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
	  <pubDate>2018-01-29T10:30:00+05:30</pubDate>
	  <guid>https://fantasy11team.com/IndU19-vs-paku19</guid>
	  <description><![CDATA[
	     <p>Welcome to the 2nd semi-final of 2018 Under 19 ICC Cricket World Cup. 
We will be providing match predictions, probable XI, tips and some tricks to help you win big in this match.
This match is going to be awesome as it is not just an ICC event but it is India vs Pakistan.</p>

<h5 id="event-details">Event Details</h5>
<p><strong>ICC Under 19 World Cup</strong> <em>Ind-Y vs Pak-y</em></p>
<ul>
  <li>Hagley Oval, Christchurch</li>
  <li>Date: Jan30, 3:00 AM IST</li>
</ul>

<h5 id="squads">Squads</h5>
<h6 id="india-u19">India U19:</h6>
<p>Prithvi Shaw(c), Manjot Kalra, Shubman Gill, Harvik Desai(w), Riyan Parag, Abhishek Sharma, Kamlesh Nagarkoti, Anukul Sudhakar Roy, Shivam Mavi, Shiva Singh, Ishan Porel, Aryan Juyal, Arshdeep Singh, Pankaj Yadav, Himanshu Rana, Aditya Thakare</p>

<h6 id="pakistan-u19">Pakistan U19:</h6>
<p>Muhammad Zaid Alam, Rohail Nazir(w), Ammad Alam, Hasan Khan(c), Mohammad Taha, Saad Khan, Muhammad Musa, Shaheen Afridi, Suleman Shafqat, Arshad Iqbal, Imran Shah, Mohammad Ali Khan, Munir Riaz, Ali Zaryab, Muhammad Mohsin Khan</p>

<h5 id="key-players">Key Players</h5>
<h6 id="india-u19-1">India U19:</h6>
<ul>
  <li>Shubhman Gill</li>
  <li>Prthvi Shaw</li>
  <li>Anukul Sudhakar Roy</li>
  <li>Kamlesh Nagarkoti</li>
  <li>Abhishek Sharma</li>
  <li>Shivam Mavi</li>
</ul>

<h6 id="pakistan-u19-1">Pakistan U19:</h6>
<ul>
  <li>Muhammad Ziad Alam</li>
  <li>Hasan Khan</li>
  <li>Shaheen Afridi</li>
  <li>Ali Zaryab</li>
</ul>

<h5 id="ind-y-vs-pak-y-probable-playing-xi-">Ind-Y vs Pak-Y Probable Playing XI :</h5>
<h6 id="india-u19-2">India U19:</h6>
<p>Prithwi Shaw, Manjot Kalra, Shubhman Gill, H Desai, Himanshu Rana, Abhishek Sharma, Anukul Sudhakar Roy, K Nagarkoti, Shiva Singh, Shivam Mavi, Ishan Porel</p>

<h6 id="pakistan-u19-2">Pakistan U19:</h6>
<p>Muhammad Zaid Alam, Rohail Nazir, Ammad Alam/M Mohsin Khan, Ali Zaryab, Mohammad Taha, Saad Khan, Hasan Khan, Shaheen Afridi, Muhammad Musa, Suleman Shafqat/M Riyaz, Arshad Iqbal</p>

<h5 id="dream-teams">Dream Teams</h5>

<p><img src="assets/images/ind-vs-pak.png" alt="Dream Tems" /></p>

<h5 id="suggestions">Suggestions</h5>
<ul>
  <li>Both the wicket keepers H Desia and R Nazir are good.</li>
  <li>Indian batsmen would be good choice to have as they are very pro.</li>
  <li>in All rounders, Anukul, Hasan Khan and K Nagarkoti are good.</li>
  <li>S Mavi is speed star in this tournamnet so it would be good choice.</li>
</ul>

<p>Let us know your favourite team and your favourite players.</p>

	  ]]></description>
	</item>

	<item>
	  <title>Delhi Daredevil buys a 17 year Old Youngster</title>
	  <link>https://fantasy11team.com/ipl-dd</link>
		
				
		
				
						<author>Rexer</author>
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
				
		
	  <pubDate>2018-01-29T08:30:00+05:30</pubDate>
	  <guid>https://fantasy11team.com/ipl-dd</guid>
	  <description><![CDATA[
	     <p>In IPL 2018 auction undergoing in Bangalore, Delhi Daredevil ipl team has bought a 17 year old Nepalese cricketer.</p>

<p>Sandeep Lamichhane will be joining the DD squad for this season’s IPL.</p>

<p>He came into the lime light after his performance in 2016 Under-19 Cricket World Cup. Afther that he was invited to play in oen of the Sydney-based clubs.</p>

<p>In January 2018, he was included in the list of players for auction in the 2018 Indian Premier League where his base price is 20 lakhs INR.He has been bought by Delhi Daredevils at his base price and became the first Nepalese player to get an IPL contract.</p>

<p>In January 2018, he was named in Nepal’s squad for the 2018 ICC World Cricket League Division Two tournament.</p>

<p>Sandeep (born 2 August 2000) is a Nepalese cricketer. He made his List A debut in the 2015–17 ICC World Cricket League Championship on 16 April 2016 against Namibia. Prior to his List A debut, he was named in Nepal’s under-19 squad for the 2016 Under-19 Cricket World Cup. In September 2016 Lamichhane received a letter from former Australian captain Michael Clarke, inviting him to play at the Sydney-based Western Suburbs District Cricket Club.</p>

	  ]]></description>
	</item>


</channel>
</rss>
