<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>

<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<channel>
   
      <title>https://fantasy11team.com/</title>
   
   <link>https://fantasy11team.com/</link>
   <description>Platform to help build a better dream team</description>
   <language>en-uk</language>
   
   <title>
   <![CDATA[ Fantasy11Team.com ]]>
   </title>
   <description>
   <![CDATA[ Platform to help build a better dream team ]]>
   </description>
   <link>https://fantasy11team.com/</link>
   <image>
   <url>https://fantasy11team.com/assets/images/favicon.png</url>
   <title>Fantasy11Team.com</title>
   <link>https://fantasy11team.com/</link>
   </image>
   <generator>Jekyll 3.6.2</generator>
   <lastBuildDate></lastBuildDate>
   <atom:link href="https://fantasy11team.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
   <ttl>60</ttl>
   <atom:link href="rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
   
	<item>
	  <title>Guide For Buying The Best Laptop</title>
	  <link>https://fantasy11team.com/How-to-choose-the-best-laptop</link>
		
				
		
				
						<author>Kapil Mittal</author>
				
		
	  <pubDate>2018-02-03T09:00:00+05:30</pubDate>
	  <guid>https://fantasy11team.com/How-to-choose-the-best-laptop</guid>
	  <description><![CDATA[
	     <p>Let’s get started!!</p>

<p>You want to buy a laptop but you don’t know how to decide which laptop you should buy, what are the configurations, what are tech factor which determines a good laptop. 
Don’t worry. We are here to help you out.</p>

<p>We will list down the major attributes you should be looking before you decide on buying a laptop.</p>

<h6 id="brand"><u>Brand</u></h6>
<p>This is one of the main factors as you don’t want to buy a laptop from a company which doesn’t care about you once you have bought their device. Go for a company which provides good customer care service and also which can deliver the service to your home as well.
We will list down major players in this area which can narrow down your search a little bit.</p>
<blockquote>
  <ul>
    <li>HP</li>
    <li>Dell</li>
    <li>Lenovo</li>
    <li>Acer</li>
    <li>Asus</li>
    <li>Apple</li>
    <li>Microsoft</li>
  </ul>
</blockquote>

<h6 id="screen-size"><u>Screen Size</u></h6>
<p>Laptop comes with different screen sizes which are measured diagonally. Screen size determines the whole size of the laptop. Some people like big screens while others like it not bulky. Depending on the choice you can select one of the screen sizes listed below. <em>In our opinion 14 inch screen laptop is the most apt laptop.</em></p>
<blockquote>
  <ul>
    <li>15.6’</li>
    <li>14.0’</li>
    <li>13.3’</li>
    <li>12.0’</li>
    <li>11.6’</li>
    <li>10.1’</li>
  </ul>
</blockquote>

<h6 id="processor"><u>Processor</u></h6>
<p>Processor is the main component of computer system which determines the processing speed and capabilities of the system.
There are many manufacturers of processor among which Intel is the prominent brand. 99% laptops come with Intel processors in them.
As of now, Intel has developed many processors with many generations. We will list out the Intel Processors which you should look for while selecting a laptop.</p>
<blockquote>
  <ul>
    <li>Intel i7 7th Generation</li>
    <li>Intel i7 6th Generation</li>
    <li>Intel i7 5th Generation</li>
    <li>Intel i5 7th Generation</li>
    <li>Intel i5 6th Generation</li>
    <li>Intel i5 5th Generation</li>
  </ul>
</blockquote>

<h6 id="primary-storageram"><u>Primary Storage(RAM)</u></h6>
<p>Primary storage, also known as RAM is the second component on which your system’s speed is dependent. The latest technology in RAM in DDR4. Others are DDR3 and DDR2. DDR2 is very old now so you can go with DDR3 or DDR4. RAM also comes in different sizes like 4GB,6GB and 8GB. Just remember, once you buy a laptop, you can not increase its RAM unlike Desktops.</p>

<h6 id="secondary-storage"><u>Secondary Storage</u></h6>
<p>Secondary storage is required to store your documents, files, movies, audios. As of now there are 2 versions of secondary storage.
Selecting SDD over HDD will highly impact the price of laptop.</p>
<ol>
  <li><strong>HDD</strong> : Most of the laptops comes with HDD storage and comes in different capacities like 512GB and 1TB(1024GB). This storage is cheap as compared to SDD but it is little slower.</li>
  <li><strong>SDD</strong> : SDD storage is fast but it is very costly.</li>
</ol>

<h6 id="operating-system"><u>Operating System</u></h6>
<p>When you buy a laptop, you get 2 options. Either you can buy a laptop with already installed Operating System(OS) on it(<em>In most of the cases Windows is already installed and laptop price is including the Operating System</em>) OR you can choose a laptop without OS(<em>means with DOS installed</em>) and install it later. In Second option, your laptop price will be lower as compared to the first option.</p>

<h6 id="additional-things"><u>Additional Things</u></h6>
<blockquote>
  <ol>
    <li><strong>LAN Port</strong>: If you don’t have wireless network at your home and you directly have connection from your internet provider, then you need this port in your laptop so that you can directly connect the wire to you laptop.</li>
    <li><strong>USB Port</strong>: Check the number of ports and if they are USB 3.0 or USB 2.0. USB 3.0 is faster in transferring data as compared to 2.0.</li>
    <li><strong>Keyboard Quality</strong>: Check the keyboard quality before making the purchase.</li>
    <li><strong>Graphic Card</strong>: If you are looking for a laptop for heavy gaming then you should check the laptops with graphic card of 1GB/2GB/4GB(from Nvidia or AMD).</li>
  </ol>
</blockquote>

<p>We hope this guide has given you some insight in selecting a laptop.
Let us know if you want any help in finding a suitable laptop for you. Just comment in the bloe section and we will get back to you.</p>

	  ]]></description>
	</item>


</channel>
</rss>
